(Sheldon:)Yes.
Yeah? Oh, well,
(Sheldon:)was this guy Rick from
Computer Solutions on Colorado?
(Sheldon:)Yes.
(Sheldon:)Yeah, well,
he does know his stuff.
(Leonard:)After you wrap the body
in reflective tape,
(Leonard:)the ends get Teflon tape
so we can get a tight seal.
Like this? Oh.
Yeah, perfect.
(Leonard:)And it helps to have
small, delicate fingers.
(Leonard:)So don't be discouraged
if you can't do it as fast
as me and Howard. (chuckles)
(Howard:)I don't know
if we have enough solder
(Howard:)to finish
these circuit boards.
(Leonard:)We had a full spool yesterday.
(Howard:)What can I say,
(Howard:)I play hard,
I solder even harder.
(Bernadette:)Sometimes he solders at home
with his shirt off.
(Bernadette:)It's like a beer commercial.
(blows, clicks tongue)
(Leonard:)Well, we got to make a run
to the hardware store.
(Penny:)How can you call yourself a
scientist and run out of solder?
(Leonard:)Well, funny story.
So, we have plenty
(Leonard:)of the 60/40
tin-to-lead ratio solder,
(Leonard:)but the spools look a lot
like the 63/37 tin-to...
(Penny:)Honey, honey,
(Penny:)honey, let me stop you.
That is-is not a funny story.
(Howard:)You want to come with us?
(Bernadette:)I'm kind of getting
into the groove here.
(Penny:)Yeah, you guys run
(Penny:)to the store and let the women
handle the science for a change.